So our next step is going to be conditioning the hair.
After you are done applying a chemical to your hair you are going to feel that it is a bit dry.
So you are going to want to use a moisturizing condition to kick some moisture back in there.
So what we are going to is start by putting the conditioner in your hand, mixing it up and pull it through your ends.
Taking it by section by section at least the first time you have done the chemical service take it section by section.
Then go back in and massage it into your scalp cause you are going to want to moisturize your hair.
It is going to be very dry, it is going to be thirsty so we are going to feed it.
Pull it through your hands and then what you can do is go ahead and grab your wide tooth comb.
Take it in sections and just comb it through your ends.
Take it in sections and comb it through your ends.
This may seem that it is a long process but it is going to help especially at the end when you rinse it and get rid of any tangles that you might have.
Just go ahead and go to our next step.